<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Formula 1 blog</title>
    <link>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Formula 1 blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>About Us Welcome to the Formula 1 Enthusiast Blog!
Who We Are We are passionate about Formula 1 racing and created this blog to share our love for the sport. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned fan or new to the world of F1, our goal is to provide engaging and insightful content that captures the excitement of each race.
What We Cover Race highlights and summaries Driver profiles Team updates and news Behind-the-scenes stories Connect With Us Follow us on social media and subscribe to stay up-to-date with the latest in Formula 1!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Hugo and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/lesson/</guid>
      
      <description>Lesson: Getting Started with Hugo and GitHub Pages Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s lesson, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the powerful static site generator, Hugo, and learn how to leverage GitHub Pages to host our Hugo-generated site. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or looking to advance your skills, this lesson will cover the essentials to get you started and take you to the next level.
What is Hugo? Hugo is a fast and flexible static site generator written in Go.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Turkish Grand Prix - Istanbul Park</title>
      <link>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/turkey/</guid>
      
      <description>Race Highlights The 2020 Turkish Grand Prix at Istanbul Park on November 15 provided a spectacular showcase of racing on a challenging wet track. The rain added an extra layer of complexity, testing the drivers&amp;rsquo; skill and adaptability.
Winner: Lewis Hamilton &amp;ldquo;These are the races you live for. The conditions were tough, but the team and I navigated it well. Proud of this win!&amp;rdquo; - Lewis Hamilton
Lewis Hamilton secured another victory, demonstrating his prowess in adverse weather conditions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Italian Grand Prix - Monza</title>
      <link>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/monza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xnadhmi.github.io/hugo-project/en/posts/monza/</guid>
      
      <description>Race Highlights The 2020 Italian Grand Prix at Monza was a thrilling spectacle filled with unexpected twists and intense competition. Held on September 6, the race delivered excitement from start to finish.
Winner: Pierre Gasly &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a dream come true! The team did an amazing job, and I&amp;rsquo;m so proud of what we&amp;rsquo;ve achieved together.&amp;rdquo; - Pierre Gasly
In a surprising turn of events, Pierre Gasly of AlphaTauri claimed victory, securing his first-ever Formula 1 win.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
